Guide to the Stanford University, University Events and Services, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, University Events and Services, records
1918-1989
1946-1989
SC0179
Stanford University. University Events and Services.
47 Linear feet
Records of the Office and its administrative body, the Committee on Public Events, include minutes, correspondence, memoranda, contracts and agreements, printed materials about events and participants, and clippings. Events include lectures, film series, Shakespeare festivals, concerts, theater performances, and distinguished visitors; the office is also responsible for the University's commencement activities.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfers, 1977-1986, 1996.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
University Events and Services, formerly known as the Office of Public Events and the Office of Public Exercises, is responsible for organizing public events on campus, scheduling University facilities, and handling publicity.
Description of the Collection
Records of the Office and its administrative body, the Committee on Public Events, include minutes, correspondence, memoranda, contracts and agreements, printed materials about events and participants, and clippings. Events include lectures, film series, Shakespeare festivals, concerts, theater performances, and distinguished visitors; the office is also responsible for the University's commencement activities.
Access Terms
Stanford University -- General subdivision--Public services.;; Stanford University. Committee on Public Events.; Stanford University. Office of Public Events.; Stanford University. Office of Public Exercises.; Stanford University. Summer Festival of the Arts.; Stanford University. University Events and Services.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1986-030
  - Tuesday evening lecture series, 1964-65 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Tuesday evening series, 1964-65 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - _______, subcommittee, 1962-66 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tuesday evening lecture series, 1965-66 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - _______ (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - F-J Miscellaneous (A & A file) 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - University lectures 1969-70 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lecture materials, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University lecture committee, minutes, 1970-71 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University lectures, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - University lecture committee, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - _______ (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Tuesday evening lecture series, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Tuesday evening lectures, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lecture evaluation forms, 1972-72 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - University lecture committee, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Committee on lectures, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Lectures by Jurgen Moltmann, March 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - bd vol: The Harry F. Camp Memorial Lectures. The Federal Congress: The Dying Branch of Government? Mark E. Talisman, 1972 (Box 1)
  - bd vol: The Harry F. Camp Memorial Lectures. November 1972 [Rene Girard, Clifford Geertz, and Geoffrey Hartman] (Box 1)
  - bd vol: The Raymond Fred West Memorial Lectures. March 1974 [Jurgen Moltmann] (Box 1)
  - Chron files dating from January 1978 to January 31, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Chron files, January 1975 to December 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1to12)
  - [Chron file] March 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - [Chron file] February 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - _______, January 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Commencement, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - _______, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - _______, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - _______, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - _______, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - _______, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - _______, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - _______, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Commencement files, 1969-1973 (Box 4)
  - Commencement files, 1974-1978 (Box 5)
  - Commencement files, 1978-1981 (Box 6)
  - Commencement files, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Commencement files, 1982 (Box 8)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1996-192
  - Funding letter, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1983 (Oct. - Nov.) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1984 (Feb. - April) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1984 (Sept. - Dec.) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1985 (Jan. - June) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1985 (Oct. - Dec.) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1986 (Jan. - April) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1986 (Oct. - Dec.) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1987 (Jan. - Feb.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1987 (March - April) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1987 (Oct. - Dec.) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1988 (Jan. - April) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1988 (November) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1988/89 miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1989 (Feb. - March) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - University Lecture Fund, 1989 (Oct.) - 1990 (March) (Box 2, Folder 7)